ANH BERNHARDT

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING STUDENT

ABOUT ME

Passionate software engineering graduate from the University of St. Thomas with 2 years experience in software and front-end development. Have developed 4 websites, 5 webapps and a mobile app. Seeking to use proven skills in software engineering and design to meet business needs.

CONTACT

Email:

anhbernhardt@gmail.com

Phone:

612-203-8821

Website:

anhbernhardt.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/anhbernhardt/

EDUCATION

University of St. Thomas

MS in Software Engineering 2019 - Dec 2021

GPA: 3.72

Bemidji State University

BS in Design

Graphics, Exhibit, and Studio Arts

2013 - 2018 GPA: 3.58

SKILLS

Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Python, SQL

Frameworks/Tools

React, Gatsby, Node, Express, Git, MongoDB, React Native

Design

Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop

PROJECT

anhnguyen.page

Personal Portfolio Website

- This is v2 of my portfolio design.
- Developed website using Ruby, Gulp, Jekyll, and host with gh-Pages.

Loan Calculator

Web Application

- Loan calculator is a web app used to calculate interest allows different user input.
- · Developed app using React.

Poncho.club

Social Website

- Poncho is a social website for virtual gatherings in Final Fantasy 14.
- Developed app using Gatsby and hosted by Netlify.

Financial Calculator

Desktop Application

- Financial calculator is a desktop app used to calculate interest allows different user input.
- Developed app using Java and SceneBuilder.

EXPERIENCE

WORKSHOP & Chicago Exhibit Production, Inc.

3D Rendering | Exhibit Designer

Aug 2018 - Oct 2018

- Modeled and edited exterior and interior of a store space from a sketch for Google Pixel that might display at Rakuten.
- Designed and presented 3D model and graphics concept of exhibit space for Versity inc as a new client potential attending the Health Trade Show.

Exhibit Partners. LLC.

Exhibit Design Intern

May 2017 - July 2017

- Modeled and presented a new concept of Tabasco's booth for future exhibit shows by using the beMatrix frame system.
- Created a future welcoming interior company spaces, as well as improve and expand upon existing design areas.

Technology, Art & Design Department

Large Format Designer

Aug 2016 - May 2018

- Led a team of 3 designers from the department to create designs and models that effectively capture the identity of TAD Talks, BSU department's TED Talks.
- Art directed and designed merch, wayfinding, and stage decoration for 200+ guests and students at the annual event.
- Hosted workshops to operate machinery and design methods throughout the academic year.